{
    "id": "92693c3041d8422790fae1c34042ebf4",
    "title": "If or unless?",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ad7d77f159ae4a3898390c790e5bd153",
            "title": "If Or Unless",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I will take the job ……………………… the pay is too low.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She will not buy the house …………………… .. you lower the price.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They will not come ……………………… you invite them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You will not lose that belly fat ………………… you do not exercise.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s go for a walk – ………………… you are too tired.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. you stop smoking, you will get cancer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Unless",
                        "If"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wouldn’t be able to do it, …………………. she didn’t help me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She will be very upset ………………… .. I don’t wish her on her birthday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… .. you give me the keys, I will kill you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Unless",
                        "If"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………… you don’t leave this place at once, I will call the police.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}